{
  "python": [
    {
      "topic": "Printing",
      "notes": "Bla-bla",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Question 1: What is the output of: print(\"Garage48\")?",
          "hint": "The result after execution",
          "answer": "Garage48",
          "options": [
            "print('garage48')",
            "Garage48",
            "Error"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "Question 2: What should be instead of __: print(\"__\") : 'is'",
          "hint": "The element that needs to be displayed",
          "answer": "is",
          "options": [
            "is",
            "None",
            "Error"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "Question 3: What is the output of: print(\"fun! :)\")",
          "hint": "The result after execution",
          "answer": "fun! :)",
          "options": [
            "fun!",
            "Error",
            "fun! :)"
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "topic": "Objects",
      "notes": "Another bla",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "What is the output of [1, 2, 3] + [4, 5, 6]?",
          "hint": "Concatenation of two lists",
          "answer": "[1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6]",
          "options": [
            "[1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6]",
            " [1, 2, 3],[4, 5, 6]",
            "21"
            ]
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the output of elem = ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd', 'e'] \n print(elem[10:])?",
          "hint": "The result after execution",
          "answer": "[]",
          "options": [
            "None",
            "[]",
            "Error"
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "ruby": [
    {
      "topic": "Mixins",
      "notes": "Bla-bla",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "What is the following function compares elements of both dictionaries dict1, dict2?",

          "hint": "Concatenation of two elements",
          "answer": "cmp(dict1, dict2)",
          "options": [
            "cmp(dict1, dict2)",
            "dict1.cmp(dict2)",
            "None"
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "topic": "Rails",
      "notes": "Another bla",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Rb Random Object Question 1",
          "hint": "Random Hint 1",
          "answer": "Random Object answer1"
        },
        {
          "question": "Rb Random Object Question 2",
          "hint": "Random Hint 2",
          "answer": "Random Object answer2"
        },
        {
          "question": "Rb Random Object Question 3",
          "hint": "Random Hint 3",
          "answer": "Random Object answer3"
        },
        {
          "question": "Rb Random Object Question 4",
          "hint": "Random Hint 4",
          "answer": "Random Object answer4"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}